Claire Hardman

Junior Full Stack Developer

Stockholm/ Valencia | +46 763416772 | chardma3.github.io/hardman-dev | github.com/chardma3 | linkedin.com/in/claire-hardman-862a558b | hardmanphoto.se | hardmanmusicofficial.com

SKILLS

Technical skills

HTML | CSS | JavaScript |
Python | Bootstrap |
Jquery | Django | Flask |
Mongo DB | SQL | Stripe |
AWS | Heroku | Github |
Slack | Google Meet

Transferable skills

Highly organised

Attention to detail

Love learning

Solution Oriented

Excellent verbal & written

Self-starter Leadership skills Efficient

Positive & Social Creative-thinker

Other Programs

Photoshop | Lightroom |
Capture One | Final Cut
Pro X | Adobe Premiere |
Avid | Ableton | Word |
Excel | Logic Pro X

Languages
English (Native)
Swedish (C2)
Spanish (A2)

Hobbies
Drums
Theatre
Volleyball

I am a Junior Full-Stack Development graduate from Code Institute 2021. I have diverse and extensive experience in a number of fields from video editing to photography to music and the entertainment industry. I am a fantastic communicator, have amazing organisational skills, am a self-starter and can work solo as well as well as enjoying working collaboratively in team environments. I bring my previous wealth of experience to every project I work on. I am thorough, have excellent attention to detail, am effective and a positive and social person. I have always been interested in tech and am always looking at how to create a better user experience.

EDUCATION

Code Institute

University Accredited Diploma in Software Dev (2021)

Milestone Project 4

HTML | CSS | JQuery | Python | Django | Bootstrap | AWS | Heroku | Git | Stripe | SQL https://hardman-photo.herokuapp.com

Milestone Project 3

HTML | CSS | JQuery | Python | Bootstrap | MongoDB | Heroku | Git | Flask https://best-bars.herokuapp.com

Milestone Project 2

HTML | CSS | JQuery https://chardma3.github.io/SummerMemories

Milestone Project 1

HTML | CSS | JQuery | Python | Bootstrap | https://chardma3.github.io/Capino

Armidale Film & TV School (TAFE, NSW, AUS)

Diploma in Screen with Distinction (2005)

Direction | Video editing | Cinematography | Production | Sound Design

WORK EXPERIENCE

DJ/Producer

Claire Hardman Music (2010-present)

Working consultative with client before and during event to cater to demographic

Photographer/videographer

Hardman Photo (2011-present)

Frilance photography/retouching projects for private individuals and companies

Photographers Assistant

Photographer Pelle Lundberg AB (2016-2019)

Setting up lighting | Troubleshooting | Welcoming crew and clients | Maintaining equipment

Studio Assistant

H&M Photo Studios (2018)

Opening & closing studios | Setting up lighting, cameras & computers | Troubleshooting | Welcoming crew and clients | Maintaining equipment